[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the actor who knew, You should always serve white wine with fish and Chianti with census takers.?", "correct_answer": "Anthony Hopkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Buscemi", "Tony Perkins", "Will Patton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of ant causes a lot of allergic reactions in the USA.", "correct_answer": "Fire ant", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Jumper  ant", "Bulldog ant", "Western brown ant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Its better to be dead and cool than alive and uncool. is a quote from what 1991 action film?", "correct_answer": "Harley Davidson and the Marlboro Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Desperado", "Easy Rider", "Broken Arrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was the peasant in Scene two (Bring out yer dead!) of Monty Python and the Holy Grail able to discern that Arthur was a king?", "correct_answer": "E doesnt got shit all over im.", "incorrect_answers": ["Es got a band o cohorts!", "Es got all that fancy armour on im.", "E looks right snooty, to me."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tragedy, written by  Shakespeare, is often referred to as The Scottish Play by actors, as it was believed that using its actual name in theatre would bring bad luck.", "correct_answer": "Macbeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamlet", "The Merry Wives of Windsor", "Othello"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this comedy - horror film, Dr. Everett Von Scott is a scientist who rivals Dr. Frank-N-Furter.", "correct_answer": "The Rocky Horror Picture Show", "incorrect_answers": ["The Texas Chain Saw Massacre", "The Exorcist", "Carrie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the following pairs (month - the gem associated with it) is wrong.", "correct_answer": "February - Peridot", "incorrect_answers": ["December - Turquoise", "March - Aquamarine", "June - Pearl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital city of the country of Papua New Guinea?", "correct_answer": "Port Moresby", "incorrect_answers": ["Madang", "Wau", "Lae"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the title of the national anthem of Egypt, Bilady, Bilady, Bilady?", "correct_answer": "My country, my country, my country", "incorrect_answers": ["Amazing, amazing, amazing", "Sing, sing, sing", "Blessed, blessed, blessed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many moons does Neptune have?", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "None", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing Ted and Joanna in this 1979 Robert Wenton movie won the Best Actor in a Leading Role and the Best Actress in a Supporting Role Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "Kramer vs. Kramer", "incorrect_answers": ["Chariots of Fire", "Crash", "Network"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Pyrenees-Mediterranean region is located along the border of which two countries?", "correct_answer": "France - Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["France - Italy", "Norway - Sweden", "Spain - Portugal"]}]